* Apple
* Desktops
* Laptops
* Phones
* Tablets
* Monitors
* Everything Else
* Services
* About Refurbished

Need help?

01428 707900

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

Back

* Sectors

Back

Back

 Clear

All categories All categoriesaccessorycustomdesktopimaclaptopmonitorSHOPSTORM\_HIDDEN\_PRODUCTtablet

Close

Login to my account
-------------------

Enter your e-mail and password:

 Email

 Password

Login

New customer? [Create your account](https://www.therenewedstore.com/account/register)

Lost password? [Recover password](https://www.therenewedstore.com/account#recover-password)

Password Trouble?
-----------------

Enter your email below to recover

 Email

Submit

Haven’t forgotten your password after all? Login here Login here

FREE 12-MONTH WARRANTY

BSI CERTIFIED

900+ 5-STAR REVIEWS

FREE DELIVERY

30-DAY RETURNS

PLANET FRIENDLY

Privacy Policy
==============

**GDPR: DATA PRIVACY NOTICE FOR CLIENTS AND SUPPLIERS**

**Introduction**

The Renewed Store Limited ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

The rules on processing of personal data are set out in the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”).

### **Definitions**

**Data controller** - A controller determines the purposes and means of processing personal data.

**Data processor** - A processor is responsible for processing personal data on behalf of a controller.

**Data subject –** Natural person

**Categories of data: Personal data and special categories of personal data**

**Personal data** - The GDPR applies to ‘personal data’ meaning any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified by reference to an identifier (as explained in Article 6 of GDPR). For example, name, passport number, home address or private email address. Online identifiers include IP addresses and cookies.

**Special categories personal data -** The GDPR refers to sensitive personal data as ‘special categories of personal data’ (as explained in Article 9 of GDPR). The special categories specifically include genetic data, and biometric data were processed to uniquely identify an individual. Other examples include racial and ethnic origin, sexual orientation, health data, trade union membership, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs.

**Processing -** means any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction.

**Third party** - means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency, or body other than the data subject, controller, processor, and persons who, under the direct authority of the controller or processor, are authorised to process personal data.

### **Who are we?**

The Renewed Store Limited is the data controller. This means we decide how your personal data is processed and for what purposes. Our contact details are: The Renewed Store Limited, Units 5&6 Colhook Industrial Park, Petworth, West Sussex, GU28 9LP. For all data matters contact Karen Champness on 01428 620604.

### **The purpose(s) of processing your personal data**

We use your personal data for the following purposes:

To fulfil an order as per customer instructions, to maintain our accounts and records and to inform individuals of news, events, or activities.

You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site, [www.therenewedstore.com](http://www.therenewedstore.com/), or by corresponding with us by phone, email or otherwise.  This includes information you provide when you search for a product, place an order on our site, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our site and when you report a problem with our site.

### **The categories of personal data concerned**

With reference to the categories of personal data described in the definitions section, we process the following categories of your data:

* Personal data:- name, company name, address, telephone number, email address.

### **What is our legal basis for processing your personal data?**  
  
**Our lawful basis for processing your general personal data:**

**Consent of the data subject;**

This means any consent that has been given to keep an individual or company informed of special offers or any other material that The Renewed Store Limited deem of interest to the individual or company.

**Processing necessary for the performance of a contract with the data subject or to take steps to enter a contract**

This means any request made by a customer to purchase from The Renewed Store Limited.  Customer details would be necessary for us perform this request and subsequently manage invoices and payment.

**Processing necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests of the data controller or a third party, except where such interests are overridden by the interests or fundamental rights or freedoms of the data subject**

This means any information that we would pass on for the purposes of retrieving outstanding debts to The Renewed Store Limited.

### **Sharing your personal data**

Your personal data will be treated as strictly confidential and will be shared, in the case of our customers, only with courier companies to deliver your goods. 

### **How long do we keep your personal data?**

We only keep a modest amount of data.  If personal data has been recorded because of a relationship with The Renewed Store Limited, although the data may not be used in future, there are various legal requirements and professional guidelines about keeping certain kinds of records – such as information needed for accounting or audit purposes.

### **Providing us with your personal data**

We require your personal data as it is necessary to perform a service for you as a customer or supplier.

### **Your rights and your personal data**

Unless subject to an exemption under the GDPR, you have the following rights with respect to your personal data:

* The right to request a copy of the personal data which we hold about you.
* The right to request that we correct any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date.
* The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary to retain such data.
* The right to withdraw your consent to the processing at any time, where consent was your lawful basis for processing the data.
* The right to request that we provide you with your personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability), (where applicable i.e. where the processing is based on consent or is necessary for the performance of a contract with the data subject and where the data controller processes the data by automated means);
* The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing.
* The right to object to the processing of personal data, (where applicable i.e. where processing is based on legitimate interests or the performance of a task in the public interest/exercise of official authority); direct marketing and processing for the purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics).

### **Transfer of Data Abroad**

We do not transfer personal data outside the EEA.

### **Automated Decision Making**

We do not use any form of automated decision making in our business.

### **Further processing**

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Data Privacy Notice, then we will provide you with a new notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions.

### **Changes to our privacy policy**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

### **How to make a complaint**

To exercise all relevant rights, queries, or complaints please in the first instance contact our Data Representative, Karen Champness on 01428 620604.

If this does not resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the [Information Commissioners Office](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/) on 03031231113 or via email [https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email/](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email/) or at the Information Commissioner's Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, England.

Last reviewed: March 2022

ABOUT

HELP

BUY

BRANDS

STAY IN TOUCH

Sign up to join the refurbished revolution and receive the latest news and offers for all things refurbished

 Your email

Subscribe

+44 (0) 1428 707900 [enquiries@therenewedstore.com](mailto:enquiries@therenewedstore.com)

Follow Us

© 2024 The Renewed Store  

© 2024 The Renewed Store  

* Opens in a new window.
